

- <u>4</u> 06/09/1996 (Thessaloniki, Greece)
- ★ Katerini, Greece
- Chistos Ziskas
- C.ziskas

My name is Christos Ziskas. I am an **ECE** with rising experience. My current ambition is to conduct further research on **new technologies**. Very importantly, I **tell the truth** on résumés and I enjoy formulating **jokes and puns** and discover new board games.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant Manager, IT Support

- Design electrical installations for Industrial Automation projects.
 - Intelligent controller (PLC/HMI) programming.
 - PV parks, Inverters, Energy Optimization
- Monitor electrical works at project sites.
- Electrical drawings to facilitate the understanding of procedures for the client.
- Troubleshooting with the team, demonstrate the installation steps .

Zalikas Liontas Construction company • October 2022 - present

IT Support Engineer

- Experience in Windows and Linux systems.
- Configuring and troubleshooting routes, VPNs and firewalls.
- Orchestrate advanced workflows for application deployment. Automating tasks and managing configurations.
- Document processes and system configurations.
- Automation management using Python and Bash.
- Containerized application deployment and management with Docker.
- Troubleshoot cloud-based environments. Experience with AWS (EC2, VPCs, S3).
- GNS3 experience in network design and simulation.

Al2Cyber - Remote ♥
August 2024 - October 2024

EDUCATION

MSc Electrical and Computer Science

Learned how to master computer science and electrical engineering, and how to utilize it in new technologies.

Chania, Technical University of Crete • 2014 – 2021

2011 2021

SELECTED PUBLICATIONS

Generating Personalized/Balanced racing game via Rolling Horizon Evolution.

MLAgents | Unity

C. Ziskas et al.

Diploma Work (2021)

DOI: ttps://doi.org/10.26233/heallink.tuc.91693 &

CERTIFICATES

Full Stack Open - Single page applications with ReactJS that use REST APIs built with Node.js

React, Redux, Node.js, MongoDB, GraphQL | Full Stack github.com/z1skgr/FullOpenStack2023

SKILLS & LANGUAGES

Software

- Java, C
- • Python

•OO Delphi

- ●●○ Bash
- ●●○ Embedded C, C#
- ••• HTML, CSS
- Development
- DockerAnsibleGit

Other tools

UnityMatlabXilinx VivadoAutocad

Languages

●●○ English

PROJECTS

SM & Omega calculations - Parallization protocols for accelerating algorithm performance

Intel Intrinsics | C

- github.com/c.ziskas/SIMD
- github.com/c.ziskas/MP

N Queen Problem - Implementation using Hill Climbing and Local Constraints

Al | Java

github.com/z1skgr/N_Queens

Portfolio - Building single page applications using Bootstrap and React

Javascript | React, Bootstrap

github.com/z1skgr/z1skgr.github.io

(MILITARY OBLIGATIONS

Support in IT office

- Archive directory from/to the headquarters
- Troubleshooting & hardware inspection
- WAN/LAN supervision for military exercises
- Research and Informatics in 24th Armored Brigade
- **a** Jan 2022 Aug. 2022
- Completed

(PERSONAL INTERESTS

- - Role games
- Track Field